{"comments": [{"comment": {"commentId": "010b9a45-95d7-ee11-904d-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1771569", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FJ026", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Appalling service", "commentText": "very long waiting times just to get to receptionist. Went in twice. First wait was 25 minutes the second 35 minutes. They lost part of the prescription in the first visit and then told me they had to reorder it. They found it at the end of the second visit after I had spent over an hour seeing whether alternative pharmacists had the item in stock.\r\n\r\ntheir telephone number was/is broken and has been for several weeks I have been told. However they hadn't informed people of this problem on the Internet or even by leaving a recorded message on the phone system. A man in the nearby doctors told me they used to be good but he has given up on them and now using another pharmacist. I would strongly advise others to do the same!", "dateSubmitted": "2024-03-01T06:31:02Z", "lastUpdated": "2024-03-01T12:41:46Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1771569", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2024}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00f74860-afd4-ee11-904d-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1768992", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FC117", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Fantastic service and help", "commentText": "The help of the Pharmacist given to me whilst working my way through the steps of sorting the NHS app was invaluable. The Pharmacist and staff are always helpful and a pleasure to deal with.", "dateSubmitted": "2024-02-26T14:00:30Z", "lastUpdated": "2024-02-26T14:28:09Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1768992", "screenName": "Mary Richards", "status": "Published", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2024}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "002f5225-61d2-ee11-9079-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1767902", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FQP25", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Helped when other pharmacies could not", "commentText": "My usual pharmacy could not supply an item from my prescription. I contacted the surgery and was told to contact other pharmacies to see if they could provide what was required. Five other pharmacies were unable to help and I was told to continue continue contacting other pharmacies. At my sixth attempt I contacted Covingham Pharmacy - what a difference! A suitable alternative medicine for me was identified, an Emergency Prescription was produced and I collected the medicine the following day. 10 out of 10 for Customer Service to Covingham Pharmacy.", "dateSubmitted": "2024-02-23T15:35:23Z", "lastUpdated": "2024-02-26T08:38:06Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1767902", "screenName": "Edward James Shaw", "status": "Published", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2024}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0184219f-c8b6-ee11-a568-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1744146", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FD357", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Absolutely Amazing Service", "commentText": "The trainee Pharmacy Tech dispensed my new medication and gave me amazing advice on the best way to take my meds, the side effects and what to do if I'm concerned. She gave amazing customer service and seem to be always willing to the extra mile.", "dateSubmitted": "2024-01-19T12:45:29Z", "lastUpdated": "2024-01-20T14:22:03Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1744146", "screenName": "Kelly", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 1, "year": 2024}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00f7ec74-6ab5-ee11-a568-6045bdcf6ff6", "commentRef": "1742381", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDA94", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Amazing staff", "commentText": "This pharmacy has helped me so very much over the last 2 years, I was diagnosed with a life threatening illness and not only have they bent over backwards for me in order to obtain my medication, they have gone out of their way to deliver it out of hours. Always available for kind words and reasurance too. 100 out of 100. Lovely lovely staff. ", "dateSubmitted": "2024-01-17T18:59:03Z", "lastUpdated": "2024-01-18T13:31:03Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1742381", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01a7694d-929e-ee11-be37-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1723893", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FWJ29", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Diabolical", "commentText": "Dreadful service. Rude staff. Repeat prescriptions are never ready regardless of how long I leave it to collect. I found out today its now owned by Enimed and the assistant informed me the pharmacist was new but apparently she's been there 7 months and still doesn't seem to have an efficient service operating. I was told to ring before collecting to see if it was ready but ironically their phone isnt working at the moment. I have now signed up with another pharmacy as I need several medications every 2 months and just want to be able to receive them without all this inconvenience. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-12-19T17:16:11Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-12-20T11:18:39Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1723893", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0127039f-4498-ee11-be37-6045bdcf6ff6", "commentRef": "1717474", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FP867", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great practice ", "commentText": "Great practice,helpful and will you help in any way,.\r\nAll take pride in there work and are very helpful to us,the customers.\r\n\r\nStill finding way round places nice to have friendly faces and great chemist \r\n", "dateSubmitted": "2023-12-11T16:45:07Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-12-11T20:40:54Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1717474", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0041a39f-2b8e-ee11-be36-00224841f497", "commentRef": "1708818", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDW12", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Rude unhelpful staff", "commentText": "Staff are so rude they completely ignore you! They struggle to get important medication but don\u2019t inform you- sometimes ask you to go back in an hour then tell you they can\u2019t get it. I asked why they couldn\u2019t let you know if they had no stock- answer was \u2018 because we have loads of customers\u2019 the amount of times I\u2019ve been told we don\u2019t have the prescription or even come home with someone else\u2019s meds is ridiculous.  Perhaps if they stopped chatting to each other and actually did their job we wouldn\u2019t have been left without insulin and dairy free baby milk on a fri tea time when they had been sitting on the prescription for days. Advising ring 111. Disgusting ! I won\u2019t be using again! ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-11-28T20:20:51Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-11-29T13:52:34Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1708818", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "007f55b6-d682-ee11-8179-6045bdcf6ff6", "commentRef": "1697365", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FT097", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Useless ", "commentText": "Went for a pre booked Covid/flu jab, called ahead, prior to parking to check appointment was still going ahead, informed yes no issues. Showed up to my appointment, after having drove to Truro specifically for the appointment and paid \u00a35 for parking, only to then be told that they have no jabs left and are awaiting more, no call in advance to people that pre booked and not told when I specifically called ahead that there was a shortage. So thanks again Reeds pharmacy for your usual poor service, I wasted trip and a waste of money having to pay for parking, rubbish service, would 100% not recommend ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-11-14T10:15:28Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-11-14T15:03:54Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1697365", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01a16af5-836e-ee11-9ae7-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1677183", "responseID": "af475155-de7f-ee11-8179-00224841fcdc", "odsCode": "FF644", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Paid for flu vaccine and no refund", "commentText": "Booked on-line for two flu vaccines. When arrived No pharmacist and door to pharmacy locked despite someone in pharmacy. Well was offering flu vaccines but not able to provide the service. Head office issued a standard apology, but still waiting for refund from the Pharmacy - and no sign of it yet! ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-19T13:32:41Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-11-10T15:32:29Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1677183", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00babeea-9878-ee11-8179-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1687040", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPG27", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent service", "commentText": "Visited Cross Chemist with my sister.  We both had our COVID 19 vaccinations.  The service was prompt, efficient and the gentleman who administered the vaccination was very pleasant and reassuring.  I would also add that it did not hurt at all!", "dateSubmitted": "2023-11-01T09:27:51Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-11-01T14:59:46Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1687040", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01527bb2-2077-ee11-8179-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1685265", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FFV56", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Highly recommended ", "commentText": "Exceptional service from this pharmacy. I am housebound and have my prescriptions delivered, all the drivers are so helpful, polite and accomodating. I would highly recommend Britton and Robson and would like to thank all the staff/drivers for their continued support. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-30T12:34:45Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-10-31T08:27:34Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1685265", "screenName": "Janet Elizabeth Lloyd", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00b11a4e-c269-ee11-9ae6-6045bdcf6ff6", "commentRef": "1671761", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FEW15", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Catastrophic Takeover of Lloyds pharmacy", "commentText": "This morning I attempted to collect two prescriptions ordered last weekend. One of them is for my 94 year old mother who depends on her medication. Paracetamol which is a basic painkiller was unavailable and the poor assistant told me that three orders had failed to be delivered. I have now had to have my medication dispensed at another pharmacy. Shame on you Jhoots for your complete lack of care.\r\nAfter reading all your reviews I'm not surprised at my own experience today", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-13T12:16:18Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-10-16T08:39:26Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1671761", "screenName": "Janet", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "012bb946-3465-ee11-8df0-00224840d45a", "commentRef": "1666697", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FLP62", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Prompt & Efficient Service", "commentText": "Just to say thank you for your professionalism. I have grown accustomed to curt and obstreperous pharmacists who hold up my prescription at the least opportunity - causing me tension & distress. One even refused me medicine prescribed by my consultant neurologist, telling me to take Paracetamol instead...\r\nI know I have a lengthy prescription, so I do appreciate the  time taken. As I am disabled and (mostly) housebound, I depend on others increasingly.\r\nWith gratitude\r\nMark Deacon", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-07T17:09:30Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-10-10T12:39:35Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1666697", "screenName": "Mark Deacon", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00d116c6-8866-ee11-9ae6-6045bdcf6ff6", "commentRef": "1667395", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FCA87", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great service", "commentText": "Had my flu jab and Bharat was so friendly and efficient at delivering my injection. Such a friendly and caring manner and can highly recommend.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-09T09:47:01Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-10-09T18:34:13Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1667395", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0141a0e1-a963-ee11-8df0-00224840d45a", "commentRef": "1665165", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FW067", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Good receptionist", "commentText": "While I waited for my Covid reception from 10am on the 5th Oct, I was very impressed by the efficient and friendly  way the receptionist\r\nhandled the almost non stop queue of cusomersas \r\n", "dateSubmitted": "2023-10-05T18:06:25Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-10-09T10:44:16Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1665165", "screenName": "Paul", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 4.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0087556d-5a5c-ee11-8def-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1658998", "responseID": "335e2875-d75d-ee11-8def-00224840d396", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "No shows", "commentText": "3 times this company has failed to keep appointments.\r\nWas given time slot for nurse visit. No show, no call, no text to provide explanation. \r\nRequested time away from work for the appointment which didn\u2019t happen. Not impressed at all. \r\nLloyds pharmacy clinical homecare offer a superior service.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-09-26T10:50:02Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-09-28T08:17:31Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1658998", "screenName": "Sara G", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01ce9c0d-775c-ee11-8def-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1659354", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FHD96", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent Service ", "commentText": "This pharmacy is second to none. Always courteous, polite and very knowledgeable about the customer. Repeat prescriptions always ready on time. Would highly recommend. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-09-26T14:14:56Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-09-26T18:50:01Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1659354", "screenName": "Kevin Cook", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01209491-5458-ee11-be6f-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1654250", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FP867", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great service", "commentText": "Wonderful experience for our covid jabs as a walk-in. Very friendly, efficient service. Booked in and boosters given within 10mins for myself and hubby. Would highly recommend. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-09-21T07:57:56Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-09-21T12:26:59Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1654250", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00613e40-aa53-ee11-be6f-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1650094", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FFV95", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Poor service - very disappointing", "commentText": "Since a takeover a few months ago, the front counter staff are terribly difficult to understand and also seem to have trouble understanding customers which is very frustrating.\r\n\r\nThe only server when I visited was flustered, trying to deal with four customers all at once rather than dealing fully with one and moving on to the next one.  We ended up all hoovering around the till waiting for our prescriptions.  She was going back and forth with our details and not achieving much at all.\r\n\r\nAn elderly lady in the shop at the same time of me was even asked to spell her surname of Brown numerous times.  Another man had a bar code on his phone which she took off him and wandered about with.\r\n\r\nOne lady bought a piece of paper with her name on it which the server assumed was a prescription.\r\n\r\nThere used to be a couple of servers in the evening after school/work time, now there is only one, creating queues.\r\n\r\nI order my prescription a week in advance, as I have done for years, I no longer get any text confirmation of it being ready to pick up. \r\n When I went to pick it up after 9 days, it was not made up nor was all the medication was available, so now I have to make another journey to pick up the remaining tablets.  \r\n\r\nThe shop looks shabby with hand written price tags and what seems to be a lot of discontinued stock\r\n\r\nUnfortunately the only other pharmacy in the area is run by the same company, so I am reluctant to change.   \r\n\r\nWhat a shame Lloyds Pharmacy had to go.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-09-15T09:28:39Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-09-19T07:44:13Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1650094", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 2.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "012e146e-1d4e-ee11-be6f-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1644325", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FKX29", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Rude and unhelpful", "commentText": "When trying to liase with this pharmacy the staff with 1 exception are curt, quite rude and generally unhelpful", "dateSubmitted": "2023-09-08T07:58:00Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-09-08T20:05:05Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1644325", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 2.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0174a8a6-5543-ee11-bdf3-00224841f497", "commentRef": "1636495", "responseID": "d1c2173e-8b46-ee11-be6e-00224840d45a", "odsCode": "FYX44", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great knowable service ", "commentText": "Alway a pleasure. Makes me feel welcome and always willing to chat \r\nLovely pharmacist and staff team thank you ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-08-25T14:42:53Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-08-29T16:44:09Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1636495", "screenName": "Sharon Fernando", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "009d8df3-923e-ee11-bdf3-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1631838", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FN473", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Trip to the pharmacy", "commentText": "Went to the pharmacy today as I\u2019d a problem with my foot.  Following a thorough assessment the problem was diagnosed and I was prescribed a course of antibiotics which were dispensed a couple of minutes later. In my opinion a first class service which I won\u2019t hesitate to use again. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-08-19T13:19:06Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-08-20T19:33:04Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1631838", "screenName": "John Massey", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00e94f31-4535-ee11-bdf4-6045bd1276cb", "commentRef": "1621376", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FJT41", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Not happy ", "commentText": "Wanted to speak to the pharmacist the person serving asked what it was about to which I replied I'd just like to talk to the pharmacist please she then said I had to tell her first. This has never happened before when I have requested to speak to the pharmacist they usually just get them. I know they are trained to answer some questions but if a customer requests to speak to the actual pharmacist surely we shouldn't be questioned if we choose not to be . As I said this is the first time it has happened I don't know if the person serving was new as I haven't come across her before and I do use the pharmacy quite regularly and I've never had a problem with the staff they are all very friendly and helpful. I will just add that the person who served me was not rude just adamant I couldn't speak to the pharmacist until I'd told her first Thanking you in anticipation. Jacqueline Grimley ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-08-07T17:09:48Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-08-09T14:48:35Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1621376", "screenName": "Jacqueline Grimley", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 4.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "019f33e7-3035-ee11-bdf4-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1621281", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FQ421", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Poor demeaning customer service ", "commentText": "Went on Saturday 5th to investigate a missing item on prescription. Been using a repeat service for several years and whilst the server was looking into my prescription, I could hear the locum moaning in the background saying it wasn't her problem, she then came out to say we hadn't had the prescription since Feb, despite only collecting last month and consecutive months prior. I asked for an emergency prescription and was told to call 111, I explained they had dobe an emergency prescription previously. The server as I was leaving rudely said to use a different pharmacy if I was happy knowing this wasn't my medicine as I was collecting on behalf of someone. The patient called there gp on Monday to sort and was told the prescription has been sent to tesco on Saturday, this was after we left. So not only did they accuse us of being at fault, and be rude they then ordered to cover the fact they hadn't ordered it in the first place. It appears to me they were swamped busy and instead of explaining this or looking in to matters properly before making judgement they were rude and blaming the customer. \r\n", "dateSubmitted": "2023-08-07T14:44:28Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-08-08T21:29:09Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1621281", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "018c048e-7730-ee11-bdf3-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1615700", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FD578", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great pharmacy ", "commentText": "Went to collect my prescription.  Staff friendly and helpful.  Had an enquiry and staff took time to advise me. Recommended, will definitely return", "dateSubmitted": "2023-08-01T14:27:41Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-08-01T21:03:34Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1615700", "screenName": "Tony", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "012f5971-1526-ee11-9965-00224840d45a", "commentRef": "1606614", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FM106", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Couldn\u2019t get any slower", "commentText": "If you want to waste time for hours to be told come back then get moaned at by staff cause they can\u2019t communicate with each other then wait for a call that doesn\u2019t happen to queue again to be told it\u2019s on the deliver, lose prescriptions \ud83d\ude44 complete shambles ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-07-19T09:20:06Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-07-28T19:44:05Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1606614", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01a61a37-c027-ee11-9965-6045bd1276cb", "commentRef": "1609027", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FXL15", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Closed during the day for lunch ", "commentText": "I get people need to have a break but closing the Pharmacy and having kids inside for an hour during business hours is outrageous. I come every time during my lunch break myself and there is no info about the closure during the day online. Wasted 3 trips to find out they closed the doors with kids bikes outside. Once managed to get there at 12:05 and was informed at the door by the pharmacist that they close for an hour for lunch at 12:00. Came back 13:10 and it was still closed. Management cannot organise people to take breaks at different times to keep the business running? Seems the pharmacist likes to have kids around during lunch times instead of organising appropriate cover for the business to keep running. How unfortunate for patients! If only there would be information online I wouldn\u2019t waste several trips to find out they can\u2019t even open back at 1pm after hosting their kids for lunch. People standing outside waiting for the NHS to finish their food and serve them with the meds they are paying for! This should be investigated and updated online to keep people informed. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-07-21T12:15:11Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-07-27T21:20:03Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1609027", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0042ec9c-6e12-ee11-9cbe-00224840d45a", "commentRef": "1579362", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FWF92", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent service", "commentText": "They are both polite and give a very quick service and their stock levels are better than other local pharmacies including Boots", "dateSubmitted": "2023-06-24T09:08:00Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-06-25T11:24:00Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1579362", "screenName": "Nigel Atkinson", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 6, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00c7a67c-a900-ee11-8f6c-00224840d396", "commentRef": "1561380", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FK081", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Insensitive and unhelpful", "commentText": "Advised to go walking around to other pharmacies to obtain a medication for a sensitive medical issue. Too little direction given to the patient, no empathy and a  lack of awareness of the impact this sort of service quality has on a patient.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-06-01T18:24:08Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-06-05T09:44:59Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1561380", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 6, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0028714e-16fb-ed11-8f6d-00224841fcdc", "commentRef": "1557371", "responseID": "facfab24-fafe-ed11-8f6c-00224841fcdc", "odsCode": "FXW56", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Useless space ", "commentText": "Ignore the phone ringing and never answer and blame it on a dodgy line when questioned about it, never have what\u2019s needed and customer service is non existent ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-25T16:07:59Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-30T14:56:34Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1557371", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0130ae91-69f8-ed11-8f6d-00224840d45a", "commentRef": "1553603", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FHH81", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Unable to contact on telephone", "commentText": "I tried numerous times to contact Boots Pharmacy on Saturday morning 20th May 2023, for confirmation of whether they had forgotten to give me an item of my repeat prescription, but no one answered the phone.  As a consequence, I could find myself without continuous medication. I could not get access to my GP online service either. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-22T06:26:25Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-22T13:29:26Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1553603", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01a833c4-b1f7-ed11-8f6d-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1553400", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FA190", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "A wealth of knowledge and compassion ", "commentText": "I\u2019m a regular customer. The staff is very approachable and always try to get prescriptions ready as quickly as possible. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-21T08:30:43Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-21T19:36:16Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1553400", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00ca5503-a7f5-ed11-8848-0022483ef6d4", "commentRef": "1552013", "responseID": "f307e926-1ff6-ed11-8848-0022483ef2fb", "odsCode": "FKG66", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible service ", "commentText": "Constantly late putting my repeat in, have to chase it regularly. Seem unable to offer a consistent service and sometimes rude.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-18T18:08:44Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-19T08:28:47Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1552013", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0095037a-5eee-ed11-8848-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1544195", "responseID": "d6dde79b-77f4-ed11-8848-0022483ef2fb", "odsCode": "FLM49", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Poor customer service", "commentText": "Had email from ummanu.health, supposedly on behalf of Pharmacy 2u, urging me to book a consultation regarding a new medicine prescribed by my GP.  However, I don't know if the email is genuine, because my GP practice has never heard of ummanu.health and Pharmacy2u don't respond to email, webchat or phone.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-09T11:41:49Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-17T05:56:54Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1544195", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00f89cbf-fcf3-ed11-8848-00224841c56b", "commentRef": "1549789", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FLW92", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "unreliable", "commentText": "I received my first pack of pouches, and all was well, but things went downhill after. My contact made  an administrative error, then corrected herself and told me when my 2nd pack would arrive. That pack is now over 2 weeks overdue, their 2 phone numbers are constantly engaged and they have not answered my increasingly concerned emails. This is a poor service that has the potential to put clients at risk", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-16T15:17:24Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-16T19:46:12Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1549789", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "018f511b-7aed-ed11-8848-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1543675", "responseID": "ea7245bb-ebef-ed11-8848-002248439e1a", "odsCode": "FD551", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great Pharmacy ", "commentText": "I moved to this pharmacy after some extremely poor customer service at another nearby Pharmacy, I have found them to be extremely helpful, polite and reliable and I have been very happy with the way they have managed medication needs. Would highly recommend to others.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-08T08:27:02Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-11T11:05:32Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1543675", "screenName": "Allan William Tavener", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00d31c72-b8ec-ed11-8848-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1543511", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FWF21", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Better than GP", "commentText": "really got to know us.  Very knowledgeable.  Extremely friendly.  My first port of call before doctor surgery.   Very sympathetic and understanding.  Professional and accommodating.   Definitely recommend.  ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-05-07T09:20:46Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-05-07T13:01:52Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1543511", "screenName": "Maria Blackmore", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00c5441c-ede4-ed11-8846-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1537239", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FGK20", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "good pharmacy", "commentText": "had my booster vaccine i received prompt polite service friendly and professional nice people would give it top marks", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-27T11:17:40Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-27T12:23:21Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1537239", "screenName": "Peter", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "004a2b4d-49e4-ed11-8846-002248439e1a", "commentRef": "1536614", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FGC74", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent pharmacy ", "commentText": "After using another pharmacy for many years I decided to change.  The reason was that on several occasions my other pharmacy was not helpful. They could source medication my wife needed so I took prescription to stepping stones pharmacy they gave me a good response, and sorted medication without any problems and we have used them since. The staff are always friendly, and very helpful great service ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-26T15:45:00Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-26T19:10:55Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1536614", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "012fe3d6-13da-ed11-a7c6-00224841c56b", "commentRef": "1527021", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPN44", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible attitude", "commentText": "I phoned 11th April asking for my prescription to be delivered it was refused even though I told her I couldn't walk her attitude towards me was terrible she needs    lessons  in  customer support it says soon  there website they deliver apparently you have to be old or infirm how much more infirm is not being able to walk her attitude was totally unacceptable 0/10", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-13T15:57:08Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-13T20:49:06Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1527021", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "003d00f6-5fd9-ed11-a7c6-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1526273", "responseID": "022762ed-01da-ed11-a7c6-0022483ef2fb", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Why is this company not held accountable?", "commentText": "So...second attempt at delivery today (after you failed the last one two weeks ago with no apparent reason) and you give me a time slot of 6pm-9pm - which as I've told you numerous times, is no good for me because I work, 20 miles from home, and finish at 6pm, but I arrange to leave work early so I can be there by 6pm. Low and behold I get two missed calls at 5.25pm. As I leave work I call back and it's the delivery driver telling me he's at my house. I was fuming! I tell him he's early and he disagrees and tells me he's not early according to his delivery times. Anyway, luckily my next door neighbour is in and agrees to take it for me (they're rarely in because they take their granddaughter out on Wednesdays) but the delivery driver doesn't leave a new sharps box which I'm desperate for and obviously I'm not at home to give him my over flowing one! Absolutely totally and utterly incompetent company! Why are you not being held accountable for your repeated failings?!", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-12T18:29:31Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-13T13:49:01Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1526273", "screenName": "Nicola Liscio", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0025acc0-13d7-ed11-a7c6-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1524400", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FLT90", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Good pharmacy", "commentText": "Good team at blackbird pharmacy, pick up the phone quickly when calling to enquire about something, and when collecting prescription items, I\u2019ve not waited more than 10 minutes from walking in to leaving - the 10 mins will be when it\u2019s peak time and they\u2019re busy. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-09T20:19:02Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-10T21:18:27Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1524400", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "016191dc-10d2-ed11-a7c6-00224841c56b", "commentRef": "1520763", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FRQ49", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "How is this place still open", "commentText": "Was great little pharmacy under rowlands, had lovely caring staff. Gone shockingly downhill since Jhoots took over, staff completely uninterested in helping, rude and abrupt. Constantly messing medications up. Changed pharmacy now cos I\u2019ve had enough", "dateSubmitted": "2023-04-03T11:15:47Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-04-05T15:55:01Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1520763", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "012f775b-5eca-ed11-b595-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1514488", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FWW04", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great practice ", "commentText": "Really friendly pharmacists, efficient and reliable service. Can provide assessment and prescription for UTI directly rather than having to get a GP appointment - fantastic service for busy people", "dateSubmitted": "2023-03-24T16:10:20Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-24T20:28:07Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1514488", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "018e383d-ccc9-ed11-b595-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1513912", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FWQ65", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Wonderful pharmacy ", "commentText": "I changed pharmacy a few months ago after being left dissatisfied and found Jade Pharmacy to be a dream. They are organised with many staff serving immediately, no waiting ever, I receive text for my medication on time, they answer the phone when you ring and everyone is nice and polite. Very satisfied of their service. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-03-23T22:44:24Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-24T13:56:51Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1513912", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "013f47a4-a8c8-ed11-b596-0022483ef2fb", "commentRef": "1512513", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FW033", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Fantastic chemist", "commentText": "All the staff at the chemist go above and beyond to help nothing is too much trouble.\nI have been using the chemist for years and would not go anywhere else. ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-03-22T11:56:59Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-22T15:40:41Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1512513", "screenName": "Jackie Wootton", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00bf2b79-4fc3-ed11-b596-6045bdf1d6c8", "commentRef": "1507910", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FG889", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great service ", "commentText": "I would like to say the staff in this pharmacy are brilliant they are very caring and polite always there to help they give a great service they are very respectful thank you limelight ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-03-15T16:36:12Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-15T22:26:53Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1507910", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00cd427d-5593-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1461356", "responseID": "6fb24dfe-c0bd-ed11-83fe-002248011cab", "odsCode": "FQ898", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Impossible to contact ", "commentText": "Why have a phone line when it is never answered??? I understand that a portacabin is not fit for purpose anyway so you can't cope with the customers hence long waits so why did you take over the only other chemist there only to then close it and leave us with just this", "dateSubmitted": "2023-01-13T15:18:13Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-08T14:53:40Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1461356", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 1, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00a97546-1d40-ed11-bba2-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1390912", "responseID": "f4bdb5b9-a1bd-ed11-83fe-002248011cab", "odsCode": "FVG71", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Appalling service", "commentText": "What is going on with this pharmacy? I have never known it get so bad before. I have been trying to call them for 3 days. I must have rung them thirty times at least. Almost constantly engaged and whenever you do get a ringtone they let it ring for ages and then cut it off. As soon as you call back it is engaged!  We should have had essentials medicines delivered for two people but, after waiting in all day nobody called with them and I can't get through to find out why.I now have no choice but to go to the pharmacy to collect the medicines which defeats the point of having a delivery service. I am a carer and really can't spare the time to do this but I have no choice. I tried to ring their Head Office and guess what? - it rang out for ages and then was cut off (multiple times). Obviously this completely unacceptable behaviour is company policy!!  I need to find another delivery service.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-09-29T17:36:48Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-08T11:09:50Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1390912", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "005477d9-3bbc-ed11-83fe-00224801d454", "commentRef": "1500702", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPQ41", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Fantastic people ", "commentText": "Helped me so much with my illness and my anxiety, these are so special people,i cant thank them enough for everything they do for me thank you all so much,\n                       Yours respectfully \n                           Mr Stephen Henderson.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-03-06T16:27:59Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-03-06T20:28:39Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1500702", "screenName": "Stephen Henderson", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0030584d-f5b0-ed11-83ff-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1490012", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FQ369", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Good experience ", "commentText": "I just wanted to leave a quick review with the outstanding service I have been receiving from this chemist recently.\n\nI have noticed a new pharmacist has taken over and since he has been there I have seen some massive improvements.\n\nEven when they are extremely busy he always makes time to see me when I have a query or require advise. \n\nHe is an asset to the pharmacy.\n\nThe team do a great work for the community. Keep up the good work.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-02-20T08:05:17Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-02-21T14:24:38Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1490012", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00c95324-16ae-ed11-83ff-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1488115", "responseID": "337e6971-c3b1-ed11-83ff-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FR245", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Degrading ", "commentText": "I\u2019ve been in the chemist on a few occasions where young person waiting for there medication which they have to take there at the chemist ! The pharmacist came out handed the young lad a bag and he had to take it there in front of a packed chemist how degrading this must have been for the young lad ? Everyone watching !!! Poor lad looking at the floor as he was walking out my heart felt for him I followed him out he said this has happed before.well shame on you for treating a person like this especially when you have a room right next to where he was stood  surly you could have been more professional and take him in the room ??? I mean would you go over to someone sat down discussing personal problems with them in front of a packed chemist ??? That is someone son brother? It\u2019s the pharmacist at fault the other staff are moor professional and treat as equal ", "dateSubmitted": "2023-02-16T16:22:47Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-02-21T08:40:57Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1488115", "screenName": "Debra", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00bf953a-f3a9-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1484369", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPP94", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Wonderful service", "commentText": "I had a blood test booked, but the phlebotomist was running over and I had to leave. I went to the counter to rearrange and the person on the counter explained that they could do it for me instead of having to rebook. They were very professional and caring as I am not good with needles and they put me at ease and I didn't even feel a thing \nWould definitely rebook my test at this pharmacy.\n", "dateSubmitted": "2023-02-11T10:02:49Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-02-11T15:13:30Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1484369", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00cfad2c-26a4-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1479132", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FRP09", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Very Poor Service", "commentText": "Called in for prescription sent from doctors 24/01/23 at 1000am 3/02/23. to be told it had not been made up , this has happened regularly with my prescriptions for the past 4 months they are never ready . I asked why and was told again staff shortages . same reason as given on previous visits. I was advised by a member of staff to find another Pharmacy as the staff problems will not be rectified soon.  I am 69 years old and diabetic/copd/heart patient and need medicine every 28 days.. I was on the boots repeat prescription service til june 2022 but changed to ordering my own on line at surgery as the repeats were not ready when due and I ran out of medicine .on several occassions. The staff are very apologetic but that does not help my situation", "dateSubmitted": "2023-02-04T00:52:21Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-02-04T13:08:22Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1479132", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 2, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01cb2c86-e3a0-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1475632", "responseID": "1c7011f8-1aa2-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible, late, irregular ", "commentText": "At the start of my treatment could not get a nurse visit for at least 6 months.\nThen no welcome pack or Sharpe's bin delivered on first delivery\nTook over 3 months for them to set up my text notifications, which meant missed delivery.\nAnother occasion asked to deliver before 4pm and said a note was put on my account for this to happen. Delivered late so I was not there.\nDelivered to a pharmacy to get around this a refrigerated injection was just left out on the side. Delivery dates for two other injections were late meaning meaning injections taken late.\nLong phone waiting times. \nDelivery slots are a nightmare. I work 7-4 and have no one who lives near me who can receive the delivery. For something I need delivery every 4 weeks why can a regular slot not be set up.\nVery disappointed, the mess they have made to my delivery has meant my treatment is starting to loose effect. \nJust in the last I have spent over 2 hours on the phone with them. Communication could be better too.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-01-30T21:17:42Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-02-01T10:27:09Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1475632", "screenName": "Mark lovell", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 1, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01b5cf44-93a0-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1475123", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDC52", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Deaf?", "commentText": "Literally never answer the phone. Prescription request put it over a week ago and still no contact so going to have to go in and check myself seeing as their phone appears to be on mute 24/7.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-01-30T11:43:11Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-01-30T15:23:58Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1475123", "screenName": "George Phillips", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 2.0}], "visit": {"month": 1, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "009c90e0-fb9f-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1474796", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FK506", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Don't update covid vaccine records", "commentText": "Had a Covid vaccine here - booked via the NHS website. NHS record & Covid travel pass still not updated months later. NHS helpline say need to follow this up with the pharmacy, but the part of the pharmacy that does vaccines is never open so cannot ask why records not updated. General pharmacy staff can't help. Don't recommend going here for any treatments.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-01-29T17:39:28Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-01-29T21:20:40Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1474796", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 2.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0183d79c-af92-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1460742", "responseID": "9968df17-8995-ed11-aad1-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Contact issues ", "commentText": "I contacted this company today as a first time user. I attempted to make telephone contact with them on three occasions today just to be placed on hold for so long I could not keep waiting. I finally got through on my fourth attempt but waited another 15 mins before I actually managed to speak to someone. I had to ask questions about the delivery details, what to expect, etc as this information was not forthcoming as such. I would expect company representatives explain such matters ,especially to new clients , without needing to be prompted. Overall I was distinctly unimpressed with the service I received and hope company communication improves radically going forward.", "dateSubmitted": "2023-01-12T19:30:52Z", "lastUpdated": "2023-01-16T10:32:40Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1460742", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 2.0}], "visit": {"month": 1, "year": 2023}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01bcc35f-0387-ed11-81ad-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1451984", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPM61", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Amazing service ", "commentText": "Amazing service provided supplying vital antibiotics when there was a national shortage. Promptly responded to my query and great communication until I collected the prescription ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-28T23:00:15Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-29T13:53:06Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1451984", "screenName": "Anna Salisbury ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0055e197-6b83-ed11-81ad-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1450865", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FG128", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent Pharmacy ", "commentText": "Had to get medicine on Christmas Eve, staff were extremely friendly,polite and helpful, i will use them again instead of online pharmacy, cannot recommend highly enough ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-24T09:16:11Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-24T10:10:05Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1450865", "screenName": "John Martin", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01428a28-fb7d-ed11-81ad-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1446506", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FA449", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Superb Pharmacy", "commentText": "Excellent staff and pharmacist. All extremely helpful and knowledgeable and nothing has ever been too much trouble, always there supporting our village. We are all very lucky to have such a great facility.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-17T11:08:40Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-17T13:37:45Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1446506", "screenName": "Joanna ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01a429d8-d653-ed11-9562-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1409714", "responseID": "7bc5e2d4-5f7a-ed11-81ad-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FH669", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Amazing Pharmacy, above and beyond!", "commentText": "I cannot recommend this Pharmacy enough! I'm not someone who has suffered with many conditions in my life but I have needed meds throughout my pregnancies and the level of care, service and listening that this Pharmacy have given me has been exceptional. They always go above and beyond to help, ordering medications in quickly, ensuring they had enough for future requests and even sending me to alternative Pharmacies when they couldn't supply. Amazing work Derix! I will keep recommending you!", "dateSubmitted": "2022-10-24T20:02:58Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-12T20:59:24Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1409714", "screenName": "Claire G", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0133f35a-f976-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1440487", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDQ20", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great practice", "commentText": "Always accommodating and helpful.  Staff helpful and efficient.  Extremely convenient location adjacent to my doctor\u2019s surgery ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-08T13:08:13Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-08T19:29:18Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1440487", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "008dbc00-8775-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1438944", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FAG81", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great customer service ", "commentText": "My 19 month old was prescribed medication via an out of hours service. I had tried to get this medication from two different local (well known) pharmacies only to be told there\u2019s a supply issue and to call around.\n\nAfter calling around and either having no answer or being told they don\u2019t have it I called Hyde pharmacy - it\u2019s quite a distance for me unfortunately but the pharmacist was incredibly helpful and assured as I was making the journey he would set it aside.\n\nWhen I arrived, as promised they had the medication in stock. I was informed they are an independent pharmacy, yet the big chain well known pharmacies fail to stock what I would deem quite a standard medication.\n\nThank you Hyde pharmacy for helping me from phone to collection.\n ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-06T16:57:04Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-06T22:07:42Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1438944", "screenName": "Nataliebaxter", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0178a492-5b72-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1436640", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FJE62", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great Walk In Experience For Over 65 Flu Vaccine", "commentText": "Just a big shout out to the staff and pharmacist.  Really positive and first rate service after being let down by Boots in Huntingdon.  Can\u2019t praise them highly enough in taking me as a walk in on a busy Friday afternoon.  ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-12-02T16:08:42Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-02T20:02:24Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1436640", "screenName": "Eric", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 12, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "006c39be-ad6b-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1430958", "responseID": "7c36c441-6671-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "The App Sucks", "commentText": "I get spammed by text at least twice a week to \"Confirm Your Delivery\" but when I log into the app, it won't respond. The date is there in front of me, the medication is right but all I can do is read the information and not confirm or cancel.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-24T04:09:15Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-12-01T10:52:42Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1430958", "screenName": "Michelle Clarke", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "007ea373-f16f-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1434125", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FPN92", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Brilliant service very professional", "commentText": "I have been let down by the so called largest pharmacies in the area then I found  Cadbury Heath pharmacy, who since I have been dealing with them found them to be caring, efficient and extremely helpful", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-29T14:23:57Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-11-29T20:22:07Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1434125", "screenName": "Bunge", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "018429d7-536b-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1430751", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FR827", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Amazing staff ", "commentText": "Was in with my son a few weeks back when he took a bad turn, the pharmacist called for an ambulance and was making sure we were both okay. All staff were amazing with us, nothing was too much trouble. They are always so friendly and polite, but on this occasion they were amazing! Can\u2019t thank them enough! ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-23T17:25:36Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-11-23T20:20:35Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1430751", "screenName": "Stacey ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01732ed0-dd67-ed11-81ac-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1427988", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FC554", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Cheered me up", "commentText": "Went to pick up my prescription and I asked for a form for covid booster and flu and was told I could have it done now. It was my late husbands birthday so I was down and went in and the pharmacist was just lovely we chatted and laughed while he gave me my injections and he just cheered me up so I say thank you to him. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-19T07:43:15Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-11-21T13:11:46Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1427988", "screenName": "Joan mayhew", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 4.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0173f1bb-d466-ed11-9561-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1427134", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FHA85", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Poor customer service", "commentText": "I went in to ask the advice from the pharmacist on a condition I had.\nHe presented as both disinterested and rude. Dropped the medication on the counter with the briefest of instructions before turning away.\nAwful service\n", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-18T00:05:44Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-11-18T19:23:44Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1427134", "screenName": "Mark Taylor", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "018f4c62-a65b-ed11-9562-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1417254", "responseID": "944720ab-5e63-ed11-9561-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FXY41", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Brilliant service", "commentText": "I emailed Alisha Pharmacy to say my doctor was sending a prescription and requested that it be ready to collect that evening. Within one hour I had my medication. Great service.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-11-03T18:36:16Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-11-13T14:23:10Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1417254", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 11, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0009d563-8258-ed11-9562-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1413745", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDR38", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Disgusting Service", "commentText": "Visited at 9:15pm after an out of hours trip to a doctor, and then leaving a family member in pain at home.  After knocking on the door an \u201cAssistant\u201dcame to the window and while smirking and laughing stated the Pharmacist was on a long tea break. \u201cCome back at 10pm\u201d she said. I understand we all are entitled to allotted meal breaks but for this to be taken 1 1/4 hours before end of day was ridiculous! I was forced to travel even further afield. Very poor service. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-10-30T18:41:04Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-10-30T21:04:35Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1413745", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0158e363-524d-ed11-bba3-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1403437", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FV528", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Efficient well run pharmacy", "commentText": "Went for a flu jab, an appointment had been made so did not have to wait. Nothing to complain about.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-10-16T12:59:42Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-10-16T19:44:28Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1403437", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0030b9a2-8449-ed11-bba2-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1399747", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FEX56", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible practice ", "commentText": "My husband attended GP 11 am Monday & was informed GP was putting prescription in then & it would be ready in the afternoon. Knowing this pharmacy he left it until Tuesday am. They said they\u2019d only just received it & only had the one item -instead of giving him the one item they told him to come back Thursday? He could have done with the one item then but wasn\u2019t offered it? This pharmacy has declined over the last 2 years. So often they return prescription because they do not have & cannot get medication. I\u2019ve then gone to Morrissons & they always have the goods. Boots have bad stocking issues. Somebody isn\u2019t doing the job right?  Very disappointing made moreso that GP surgery has moved. Shawbirch GP practice are amazingly good.  Boots are abysmal ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-10-11T16:49:14Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-10-11T20:01:10Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1399747", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 10, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00eae1ed-5b41-ed11-bba3-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1391947", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FD549", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Very kind and helpful staff", "commentText": "I visit this pharmacy often as I live locally. Staff are always very patient and helpful, despite being busy. They are considerate and respectful when discussing health concerns, and the customer service provided is excellent every time. Thank you!", "dateSubmitted": "2022-10-01T07:37:42Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-10-01T10:32:25Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1391947", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01cc636a-fa3f-ed11-bba2-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1390480", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FR402", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Fantastic !", "commentText": "You have served my family for decades.  Thank You so very, very much for everything - I do not know what we would do without you.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-09-29T13:27:13Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-09-29T15:50:21Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1390480", "screenName": "David Ashford", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00d43a1d-5c3b-ed11-9db1-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1386350", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FQV39", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Accomodating", "commentText": "I highly recommend Boots Jubilee Canary Wharf, I went for my Covid booster vaccine which I have booked online via NHS however when I got to Boots and showed my booking I didn't realise the date which will be on the 29th September! The staff politely told me I got the date wrong. I apologised but asked whether there is a chance they could accommodate me but he said no. So I left but I was surprised as staff called me and told me that there is available stock and asked if I'm happy to wait for which I said I don't mind. Hence I waited and finally, this paid off as I was given my booster. So a big thank you to the staff and keep up the good work!!!\n", "dateSubmitted": "2022-09-23T16:23:56Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-09-25T10:28:59Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1386350", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00d56fc0-b739-ed11-9db1-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1384507", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FFT74", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great pharmacy", "commentText": "My husband and myself booked our Autumn Covid booster at Jp Pharmacy and were impressed by their efficiency. A lady assisted us through the registration process and showed us where to sit. There was a system where you moved up seats until it was your turn for the vaccination. Very easy, quick and painless and pleasant staff. Other people thought so as well. \n", "dateSubmitted": "2022-09-21T14:14:59Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-09-24T15:38:00Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1384507", "screenName": "Margaret ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00b1b61d-4e2c-ed11-9db2-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1375376", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FLA40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent Service & Staff", "commentText": "I have been using Colley Gate Pharmacy for the last elevent years and have found that they provide an excellent service. On the last occasion I visited I had been to the doctor's and my prescription was sent electronically to the pharmacy. Later when got home I rang the pharmacy to check that they had received my prescription. They confirmed that they had received it and that I could collect it in 15 minutes.\nExcellent service and staff.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-09-04T12:35:57Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-09-04T15:59:29Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1375376", "screenName": "BillB", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 9, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00447c76-3622-ed11-9db2-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1368302", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FMG33", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "The Worst Shop in Old Windsor", "commentText": "I've never had a good experience with this pharmacy. It is very poorly managed and the staff are arrogant and rude. I now have the opportunity to use another pharmacy and will do so.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-22T16:21:24Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-22T20:25:41Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1368302", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00e35f17-d71e-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1365813", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FJM64", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent Support and Welcoming Environment", "commentText": "The updated and enhanced facilities now in place are impressive for a local pharmacy. Staff are knowledgeable and supportive which is a welcome improvement compared to the larger pharmacy chains. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-18T09:21:14Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-18T10:51:15Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1365813", "screenName": "Charles Bevin", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01bd575d-281e-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1365174", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FYY52", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent experience ", "commentText": "I took my very apprehensive 3 year old for her chicken pox vaccination & had an excellent experience.  The staff are so friendly & put my daughter straight at ease.  The pharmacist was great, professional & yet very personable. Excellent experience, would highly recommend. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-17T12:30:32Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-17T15:49:38Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1365174", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00443c1f-6b1c-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1363336", "responseID": "657d4edf-1b1d-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FQ718", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent service", "commentText": "Went for a Booster jab. The whole procedure went very smoothly and was clearly explained.\n\nI want to thank the Volunteer, (whom I can't name) for the advice regarding name change. \n\nExcellent service. Thank you. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-15T07:23:13Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-16T04:28:42Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1363336", "screenName": "Farrukh Riaz", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "007f5e4d-b917-ed11-b83f-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1360000", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FRQ84", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Excellent service ", "commentText": "This pharmacy is excellent. They provide a swift professional service.\n\nAlways happy to help with any of your needs and I highly recommend them.\n\nStaff are professional, have great knowledge and always happy to serve their customers ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-09T08:00:24Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-09T13:30:43Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1360000", "screenName": "J Godsmark", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01258df5-4413-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1357061", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FGG50", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Out standing customer focused front desk staff.", "commentText": "Friendly ,welcoming customer focused staff . Absolute delight . suffering from carpool tunnel the lady who servered me was very knowledgeable and was able to help me sort out where to get help and by a wrist support indicate how to look after  my wrist until possible surgery in September.can not thank them more high ly ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-08-03T15:57:27Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-03T20:25:36Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1357061", "screenName": "Ian herd", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 8, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0152bfd8-c5dd-ec11-bb3c-6045bd0e68da", "commentRef": "1316295", "responseID": "2ea69066-fb12-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "odsCode": "FEV24", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Wonderful pharmacist & staff", "commentText": "Hi, I have visited this pharmacy before several times with some small things and picked up medication - everyone is always incredibly helpful and friendly (and happy!) but a few days ago, I went in with my friend regarding an issue with my tongue and explained my ongoing issues with my migraines to the pharmacist on that day & not only was he incredibly understanding and caring about my pain, which in the medical field sadly I don\u2019t come across very often in the ways he showed. But he also knew what to do for my mouth. I\u2019m still taking the tablets to hopefully everything will clear up. But I have never been seen so effectively and carefully in this system and I will remember that. So thank you. And happy 50 years in pharmacy practice to him. Hope this is helpful. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-05-27T14:03:56Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-08-03T07:11:00Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1316295", "screenName": "Tilly", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0119b67a-320c-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1351143", "responseID": "17c21834-4d0f-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FL233", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Worst service ", "commentText": "Very bad system every time you pickup a prescription there\u2019s always a problem. One time i drop off a px in the morning came back in the afternoon still not read. And a lot more issues like owing they will say will call you when its ready but they will not etc etc etc", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-25T15:57:36Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-29T14:46:29Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1351143", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "011728b4-d309-ed11-82e5-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1349873", "responseID": "594394ba-3c0a-ed11-b83e-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FQ718", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Great customer service", "commentText": "The staff were extremely nice and took care of my needs as a muslim women to advise for a female nurse when carrying out my vaccine", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-22T15:34:03Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-23T04:06:00Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1349873", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "007a9a04-e408-ed11-82e5-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1348753", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FD341", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible service ", "commentText": "Waited 15 minutes to get front of queue only to be told they could issue meds. In fact every single customer was sent away because prescriptions not ready, even those from previous week, and was told to return after 2pm. \nClearly not enough staff on duty to process prescriptions and it would appear this is a long time issue and my medication has not been available for immediate collection every time I have been there this year.\nWould have been better off closing store for morning and all staff trying to clear backlog.\n ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-21T10:58:18Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-21T17:52:37Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1348753", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01323bd8-5c03-ed11-82e6-6045bd0e7c66", "commentRef": "1344745", "responseID": "2edf3e72-3004-ed11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "I've never had a problem!", "commentText": "Having seen all the less than complimentary reviews on here, I thought it only fair to point out that people generally only post reviews that are negative but when all goes to plan, it's just expected.\n\nMy dealings with this company and it's previous guise over the years have been generally good. Today for example I sent a message to them via their contact form and received a call back from them within twenty minutes.\nI had miscalculated how much medication my daughter had left and with a holiday coming up was worried that we wouldn't have supplies for when we returned.\nThe lady (who's name I'm not allowed to mention) was very sympathetic and has arranged for a delivery to us two days before we go away. You can't ask for more than that.!  ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-14T10:08:03Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-15T11:22:52Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1344745", "screenName": "J P R", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 4.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01802209-fa00-ed11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1342491", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FFH21", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible service as always", "commentText": "Was told last Thursday that my babies prescription would be ready the next day (Friday). We never got a text to say it was ready despite leaving our number \n\nSo I came back on Monday to ask where the prescription is, the lady told me it'll be \"ready in a few minutes\". I then waited 10 minutes and the pharmacist came over and told me the medicine is on order and will be ready the next day!\n\nI mentioned how this has been on order since last week and asked why is it still on order. I was offered no explanation and was told \"it's just still on order is all but will be ready for tomorrow\"\n\nThis is the 5th time this has happened. Before, I would allow it due to the baby milk shortage, but this time it's his vitamins and actual medicine which I cannot excuse.\n\nAdditionally the customer next to me was completely forgotten about and when she asked what the delay was she was told they had forgotten to speak to the pharmacist and asked her to keep waiting while they go do that.\n\nThe pharmacy still has a 4 person occupancy limit which is no longer feasible and there's vulnerable people forced to wait outside in 31\u00b0c heat.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-11T09:15:46Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-11T10:58:06Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1342491", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 7, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "01bfde3e-fefe-ec11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1341876", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FDP25", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Poor service", "commentText": " Ordered medication as usual . Did not arrive so rang them . Told medication had gone up in price so not available ! Went to Boots instead .", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-08T20:40:49Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-08T21:13:53Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1341876", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 6, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "001e5feb-cffa-ec11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1337830", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FJX45", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Service with a smile", "commentText": "I've never been disappointed with this pharmacy. Even when there is a queue it moves steadily and customers leave with what they came for. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-03T12:59:09Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-07T15:26:56Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1337830", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 4.0}], "visit": {"month": 6, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0151ef0d-a8fa-ec11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "commentRef": "1337778", "responseID": "4335ed97-b0fb-ec11-82e6-6045bd0e76d3", "odsCode": "FTX40", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Terrible customer service ", "commentText": "This company should be removed as medication delivery service, for the 2nd time I have been left with no medication.  Can't get through on the phone as noone answers, live chat has been down for weeks for maintenance, no replies to emails ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-07-03T08:13:44Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-07-04T15:47:26Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1337778", "screenName": "Michael Prothero ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 6, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00cd6cdf-b4b1-ec11-983f-6045bd0f33e9", "commentRef": "1283861", "responseID": "7708f343-0ddb-ec11-bb3c-00224841f6ed", "odsCode": "FG273", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Smoking session", "commentText": "Been stopped smoking for nearly 2 months now thanks to the help and assistance from the stop smoking councillor.  Very enthusiastic, considerate, and understanding.  Would definitely recommend giving it a go because it's much easier now with the new stop smoking aids.  Good luck!", "dateSubmitted": "2022-04-01T12:11:40Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-05-24T02:57:40Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1283861", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00bb60ae-ebd1-ec11-a7b5-0022480700d4", "commentRef": "1306442", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FW548", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Extremely slow service", "commentText": "To say there is over 7 members of staff at the Trust Pharmacy the service is extremely slow.\nPeople do not want to be waiting more than 10/15 minutes to collect a prescription after having to see a clinic or use a service within the hospital.\nEasy take the prescription, get it ready, check it, dispense it.\nMaybe the staff or the management need training in being more productive.", "dateSubmitted": "2022-05-12T12:04:39Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-05-12T20:46:10Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1306442", "screenName": "Kevin", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 5, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "00f6520c-91c8-ec11-a7b5-6045bd100f54", "commentRef": "1299923", "responseID": "dd851ab3-f4d1-ec11-a7b5-0022480700d4", "odsCode": "FL233", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Very unhelpful", "commentText": "I called to ask for help with an emergency prescription request for my ongoing medication. They just said no they couldn\u2019t help even though I\u2019ve been a Lloyds customer for years. Eventually found a great pharmacist in Tesco who told me to go online to 111 and fill in a form and he was then able to help. I\u2019m pretty sure they must have known that it was that simple but just didn\u2019t want to help me. ", "dateSubmitted": "2022-04-30T14:23:04Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-05-12T13:09:17Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1299923", "screenName": "Anonymous", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 1.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "001270a2-2cbc-ec11-983f-6045bd0ff229", "commentRef": "1291668", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FR584", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Best pharmacy iv been too ", "commentText": "Thank you to all staff who always work so hard to get all my prescriptions ready so promptly no waiting around really appreciate you all thanks guys Bobbi k", "dateSubmitted": "2022-04-14T19:54:04Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-04-14T20:39:26Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1291668", "screenName": "Bobbi Keen ", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 3, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}, {"comment": {"commentId": "0118e6cd-69b7-ec11-983f-6045bd103eb3", "commentRef": "1288393", "responseID": "", "odsCode": "FN266", "commentOriginalURL": "", "title": "Helpful staff", "commentText": "Phoned up with query on a repeat prescription and obtained information and arrived at pharmacy with medication waiting straight away,excellent service from friendly staff!", "dateSubmitted": "2022-04-08T18:29:21Z", "lastUpdated": "2022-04-09T14:23:26Z", "sentimentScore": 0.0, "department": "", "publisherID": "0", "publishersCommentRef": "1288393", "screenName": "michael adams", "status": "Published With Edits", "removeReportLink": false, "ratings": [{"question": "10019", "rating": 5.0}], "visit": {"month": 4, "year": 2022}}, "response": null}], "totalRecords": 12764}